{
    "subject": "Paul_Spence",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "FUBAR_2__film_",
    "human_readable": "Paul Spence acted in the film FUBAR 2.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7159032225608826,
            "question": "What film did Paul Spence act in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6689357161521912,
            "question": "Who directed the film FUBAR 2?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6616093516349792,
            "question": "Who is Paul Spence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.547305703163147,
            "question": "What other films has Paul Spence been in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44533151388168335,
            "question": "Is Paul Spence a well-known actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4432823657989502,
            "question": "What is the plot of FUBAR 2?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36134031414985657,
            "question": "What genre is the film FUBAR 2?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3591766059398651,
            "question": "What year was the film FUBAR 2 released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3372778296470642,
            "question": "Has Paul Spence won any awards for his acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3289317786693573,
            "question": "Is Paul Spence a Canadian actor?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Spence acted in the film FUBAR 2.",
            "html": "yago_10058_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Paul Spence won any awards for his acting?",
            "html": "yago_10058_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film FUBAR 2 released?",
            "html": "yago_10058_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film FUBAR 2?",
            "html": "yago_10058_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10058_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10058_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10058_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10058_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10058_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10058_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10058_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10058_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10058_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10058_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Paul Spence acted in the film \"Fubar 2,\" which directly supports the statement that Paul Spence acted in the film FUBAR 2."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}